https://www.alpenwild.com/staticpage/privacy-policy/

TripsHikeBest of the Swiss AlpsExploring The JungfrauItalian DolomitesBest of the French AlpsBest of Slovenia and the Julian AlpsTrekChamonix-Zermatt Haute RouteDeluxe Haute RouteDeluxe Tour du Mont BlancDeluxe Bernese Oberland TraverseEiger to the MatterhornVia Alpina - Swiss Alpine Route RailScenic Alps by RailScenic Alps by Rail - Christmas EditionGlacier Express - Self-GuidedSelf-Guided Scenic Alps by RailFood & CultureCheese, Chocolate, & the AlpsSelf-Guided Self-Guided Haute RouteSelf-Guided Tour du Mont BlancSelf-Guided JungfrauSelf-Guided Bernese Oberland TraverseSelf-Guided Eiger to the MatterhornSelf-Guided Via AlpinaSelf-Guided AlpsSelf-Guided Austria Zillertal AlpsCustom and Guided ToursPrivate Guided and Custom TripsSwiss Alps Winter AdventureAlps Photo WorkshopIn the Footsteps of TolkienJungfrau and Saas-Fee Wildflower HikesBest of the Bernese AlpsFamily History and Swiss
Genealogy ToursBest of the Engadine & St MoritzTour Add-Ons & GetawaysAppenzell -Alpstein RangeLeukerbad -Thermal Hot SpringsEuropaweg – St. Niklaus to ZermattSaanenmöser- Gstaad HighlandsZermatt Fly FishingZermatt and the MatterhornSaas-FeeWinter ToursChristmas in SwitzerlandTour CalendarAbout Our ToursWhere We Stay How We Travel FAQ FAQ – Alpenwild Experience FAQ - Tour du Mont Blanc FAQ - Haute Route FAQ- Scenic Alps by Rail Tour FAQ - Alps Hiking Tours Travel Agents + Alpenwild Why You'll Love The Alps A Message to Our Guests - Coronavirus Plan a TripPacking Lists Packing List – Alps Trekking Tours Packing List – Alps Walking and Sightseeing Tours Packing List – Alps Hiking Tours Packing List - Christmas in Switzerland Packing List - Winter Tours Weather In The Alps Haute Route Essentials Tour du Mont Blanc Essentials Is a Self-Guided Trip for me? Car Travel in Switzerland Maps & Books Book a TripBook Your Trip Make a Payment About UsWhy Choose Alpenwild The Alpenwild Story Guides and Trip Leaders Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Alpenwild is committed to respecting your privacy and to doing everything we can to earn your trust as you use this website and travel with us. This statement summarizes our policies about the information you provide to us on this site.
What Information Do We Collect On This Web Site?
We encourage you to freely browse this site, and we do not collect any personally identifiable information when you do so, only anonymous information about the pages visited to help us make this website more useful. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, or receive other proprietary pre-trip information, we ask that you complete a short registration form.
Email Newsletter
Alpenwild offers an email newsletter, sent approximately ten times per year, providing you with information about upcoming trips, special sales, and news which we think will be of interest to you. These emails come directly from Alpenwild. When you register you have the option to subscribe to this newsletter. You may unsubscribe from our newsletter list at any time, in a variety of ways. You can reply to one of our newsletters with the word "Unsubscribe" in the subject line, you can email us and simply include the word "Unsubscribe" in the subject line. You can also call us to request that you be removed. However you do this, we will immediately remove you from the list and no longer send the newsletter to you.
Pre-trip Newsletter
If you have registered for an Alpenwild tour you will receive pre-trip information (packing lists, news, and tour updates) in an email newsletter sent in the few months prior to your trip departure. These pre-trip newsletters are especially popular with our clients. They will help you prepare for your tour and enrich your travel experience immensely. You may unsubscribe from these pre-trip newsletters at any time-though no one ever has.
Linked Internet Sites
Other internet sites which may be linked to this site may have privacy provisions that differ from this Privacy Policy. We encourage users to be aware of when they leave our site as Alpenwild has no control over and is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other such sites.
Photography
Alpenwild, its trip leaders, and Alpenwld-authorized third parties reserve the right to take photographs or videos during the operation of any tour or part thereof and to use the resulting photography, videos, or recordings for promotional or commercial use. By making a reservation on an Alpenwild tour, the participant agrees to allow their likeness to be used by Alpenwild and Alpenwild-authorized third parties, without compensation to the participant. If the participant prefers that their likeness not be used, they must notify Alpenwild in writing prior to departure of the tour.
Privacy Policy Amendments
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check our web site periodically. If you have any questions about our Private Policy please email us.
Opting Out
To opt out, please click the link below
https://app.adroll.com/optout
Get in Touch:
Sign Up for Our Email Newsletter
Stay up to date on the latest Alpenwild news. You're free to opt out at any time.
Interests:
Culture & HistoryFood & WineRailSightseeingSki & WinterTrekking/HikingWalkingSpa
See our Privacy Policy.
Submit
Email Address *
Submit
Print Itinerary
